This is exactly what I've been looking for.
这个正是我一直在寻找的.
I'm having my kitchen remodeled.
我正在改造我的厨房.
Cool.
酷.
William, look at this.
William, 看这个.
Here, she's had her nose fixed.
这里, 她把鼻子修整了.
Then, she's had her wrinkles removed.
然后, 她把皱纹移去了.
And here, she's had her behind lifted.
这儿, 她把臀部提升了.
I think it's a big deal when I get my hair cut.
我认为那是一件大事情 当我去剪头发.
Seriously.
当然.
Which, by the way, you didn't notice.
Which, 顺便说, 你没有注意到.
-But I did notice.  -What?
-但我确实注意到了.  –什么?
You got your hair cut.
你理发了.
You hate it.
你不喜欢.
It's fine. It's very nice.
很好.很漂亮.
I’m gonna have this packed up.
我要把这个包起来.
Ugh. You can get your ears flattened!
Ugh. 你可以把你的耳朵弄平!
Really, Wendy, don't change a thing.
真的, Wendy,什么都不要改.